Nevada Folklife Archive
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Photographs
  - Subseries 1: Slides, 8,390 still images (.jpg); 8,390 still images (.tif); 14,257 still images (.jpg); 14,257 still images (.tif)
    - International Food and Folklife Festival of Southern Nevada held at the Clark County Government Center Amphitheatre, May 4, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-050; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 93)
    - Great Basin Native American Basketweavers Gathering at Wingfield Park, September 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-051 - S-2002-054; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 67 color slides (35mm) (Box 93)
    - Doug Groves, rawhide braider, master artist, March 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-055; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 93)
    - Site visit to Doug Groves' working Dunphy Ranch with buildings and horses, acreage, cowboy gear and hides, March 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-056; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 93)
    - Master artist Sue Coleman presenting educational program in various Washoe County schools about Washoe basket making, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-057; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 93)
    - Master artist Griff Durham presenting educational program in various Washoe County schools about cowboy gear and tack, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-058; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 93)
    - Master artist Sue Coleman presenting educational program in various Washoe County schools about Washoe basket making, May 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-059; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 93)
    - Master Artist Zoria Zetaruk and apprentice Steve Furimsky, at Zoria's home, with pysanky (Ukrainian decorated eggs) that he has made, April 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-060; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 93)
    - Master artist David Johnson and apprentice Keith Hodges at D-Bar-J hat shop making hats from beaver pelts and felt for working ranchers, movie stars, and others, May 4, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-075; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 93)
    - International Food and Folklife Festival of Southern Nevada held at the Clark County Government Center Amphitheatre, May 4, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-076; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 93)
    - International Food and Folklife Festival of Southern Nevada held at the Clark County Government Center Amphitheatre, May 4, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-077 - S-2002-079; Christina Barr; 60 color slides (35mm) (Box 94)
    - Cinco de Mayo Festival at Lorenzi Park in Las Vegas, and Yoko Arana's Japanese embroidery class at the Las Vegas Senior Center, July 23, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-080; Christina Barr; 14 color slides (35mm) (Box 94)
    - Yoko Arana's Japanese embroidery class at the Las Vegas Senior Center, July 24, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-081; Christina Barr; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 94)
    - Girtia Lukes's quilting class at the Derfelt Senior Center, July 30, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-082; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 94)
    - Yoko Arana and Mimi Thompson demonstrating Japanese Bunka and Kogin embroidery, and serving a Japanese meal at the Las Vegas Senior Center in Las Vegas, Nevada, July 30, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-083 - S-2002-084; Christina Barr; 35 color slides (35mm) (Box 94)
    - Carrie Black - a seamstress who lives in Henderson and makes clothing for herself, her family, and people in her Latter Day Saints ward. She also sells fabric on the side, August 6, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-085 - S-2002-086; Christina Barr; 32 color slides (35mm) (Box 94)
    - Frances Buono and her recycled crafts at the Dolittle Senior Center in Las Vegas, Nevada. Frances is Italian American (originally from Brooklyn, New York) and teaches crafts to seniors, August 8-10, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-087 - S-2002-088; Christina Barr; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 94)
    - Members of the Las Vegas Buddhist Sangha preparing bento boxes for the Obon ceremonies in Las Vegas and members of the Las Vegas Buddhist Sangha dancing at the Obon ceremonies in Las Vegas, August 10, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-089; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 95)
    - Members of the Las Vegas Buddhist Sangha dancing at the Obon ceremonies in Las Vegas, August 10, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-090 - S-2002-091; Christina Barr; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 95)
    - Israel Favela in his shop at El Azteca Custom Iron Works, North Las Vegas, August 12, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-092 - S-2002-093; Christina Barr; 33 color slides (35mm) (Box 95)
    - [Unknown], August 15, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-096 - S-2002-097; Christina Barr; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 95)
    - OXS exhibit On the Road with a Folklorist in the Nevada Arts Council office, Las Vegas, August 15, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-098; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 95)
    - Monthly meeting of the Shadow Mountain Quilters quilting circle (members of the Desert Quilters' Guild) in Pahrump, Nevada, August 15, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-099 - S-2002-102; Christina Barr; 120 color slides (35mm) (Box 95)
    - Monthly meeting of the Shadow Mountain Quilters quilting circle (members of the Desert Quilters' Guild) in Pahrump, Nevada, August 15, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-103 - S-2002-104; Christina Barr; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 96)
    - Quilts made by members of the Shadow Mountain Quilters as part of a challenge quilt contest sponsored by a local fabric store in Pahrump, Nevada, August 15, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-105 - S-2002-106; Christina Barr; 35 color slides (35mm) (Box 96)
    - Barbara Griffith in her workshop, at her home in Pahrump, Nevada, August 20, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-107; Christina Barr; 12 color slides (35mm) (Box 96)
    - Barbara Griffith in her workshop, at her home in Pahrump, Nevada; Barbara Griffith and Ruth Cosgrove in Ruth's home in Pahrump, Nevada; and Victoria Brazzle in her quilting workshop at her home in Pahrump, Nevada, August 23, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-108; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 96)
    - Victoria Brazzle in her quilting workshop at her home in Pahrump, Nevada; Mohammed Darehbaghi and his paintings during the OXS opening at the Arts Council's Las Vegas offices, August 23, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-109; Christina Barr; 6 color slides (35mm) (Box 96)
    - OXS exhibit opening featuring Mohammed Darehbaghi in the Las Vegas office of the Nevada Arts Council, August 26, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-110; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 96)
    - Ullhambana celebrations at the Nevada Buddhist Association Temple in Las Vegas, August 26, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-111 - S-2002-112; Christina Barr; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 96)
    - Wilma Myers and her quilts taken at her home in Henderson, Nevada, August 26, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-113 - S-2002-114; Christina Barr; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 96)
    - Wilma Myers and her quilts taken at her home in Henderson, Nevada, August 26, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-115 - S-2002-121; Christina Barr; 131 color slides (35mm) (Box 97)
    - Susie Finlay, a Danish American fabric artist who lives in Cold Creek, Nevada. Susie spins wool, weaves, quilts, tats, makes lace, crochets, embroiders, knits, and makes clothing, August 27, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-122 - S-2022-125; Christina Barr; 55 color slides (35mm) (Box 97)
    - Zoria Zetaruk and her Ukrainian eggs taken at her home in Las Vegas, September 7, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-126 - S-2002-127; Christina Barr; 28 color slides (35mm) (Box 97)
    - Zoria Zetaruk and her Ukrainian eggs taken at her home in Las Vegas, September 7, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-128; Christina Barr; 11 color slides (35mm) (Box 98)
    - Members of the Desert Quilter's group hosting their New Members' Tea to welcome new members to their organization. The tea was held at the Sunrise Library in Las Vegas, Nevada, September 9, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-129 - S-2002-130; Christina Barr; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 98)
    - Nevada Quilt while it was hanging at the Sunrise Library in Las Vegas, Nevada, September 9, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-131; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 98)
    - Monthly meeting of the Bluebirds quilting circle (members of the Desert Quilters' Guild) at the home of Peg Cummings in Las Vegas, Nevada, September 9, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-132 - S-2002-135; Christina Barr; 78 color slides (35mm) (Box 98)
    - Girtia Lukes and her quilts at her home in Las Vegas, Nevada, September 10, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-136 - S-2002-139; Christina Barr; 60 color slides (35mm) (Box 98)
    - Girtia Lukes and her quilts at her home in Las Vegas, Nevada, September 10, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-140; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 99)
    - Dawna Jolliff and her mother's (Thelma costumes/memorabilia) at her home in Las Vegas, Nevada, September 14, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-141; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 99)
    - Jody Cotton and her quilt projects at her home in Las Vegas, Nevada, September 14, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-142 - S-2002-143; Christina Barr; 39 color slides (35mm) (Box 99)
    - Boulder City Folk Festival, Freedom Park, Boulder City, Nevada, October 1, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-144- S-2002-145; Christina Barr; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 99)
    - Thai Cultural Arts Festival held at the Charleston Heights Arts Center, October 1, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-146; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 99)
    - Marge Stanbridge and her quilt projects at her home in Las Vegas, Nevada, October 1-2, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-147 - S-2002-149; Christina Barr; 53 color slides (35mm) (Box 99)
    - Marge Stanbridge and her quilt projects at her home in Las Vegas, Nevada; Zoria Zetaruk and her students in class at the Las Vegas Senior Center in Las Vegas, Nevada, October 2, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-150; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 99)
    - Zoria Zetaruk and her students in class at the Las Vegas Senior Center in Las Vegas, Nevada, October 2-12, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-151; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 100)
    - Jill (Heckendorf) Halverson and Linda Heckendorf (Hatch) and their tatting work at Jill's home in Henderson, Nevada, October 12, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-152 - S-2002-153; Christina Barr; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 100)
    - Jill (Heckendorf) Halverson and Linda Heckendorf (Hatch) and their tatting work at Jill's home in Henderson, Nevada; Hispanic Day Parade held in downtown Las Vegas (along 4th Street), October 12, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-154; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 100)
    - Hispanic Day Parade held in downtown Las Vegas (along 4th Street). This was an election year, so many of the parade participants were politicians seeking office and Hispanic organizations supporting candidates, October 12, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-155 - S-2002-159; Christina Barr; 98 color slides (35mm) (Box 100)
    - Hispanic Day Parade held in downtown Las Vegas (along 4th Street). This was an election year, so many of the parade participants were politicians seeking office and Hispanic organizations supporting candidates, October 12, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-160 - S-2002-162; Christina Barr; 48 color slides (35mm) (Box 101)
    - Mary Sharp and her quilting, sewing, and cross stitch projects at her home in Las Vegas, Nevada, October 16, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-163 - S-2002-165; Christina Barr; 58 color slides (35mm) (Box 101)
    - Costume maker and wardrobe dresser Frieda Bronfin at her home in Las Vegas, October 17, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-166; Christina Barr; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 101)
    - Quilter Janett Rice and her quilts at her home in Henderson, Nevada, October 17, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-167 - S-2002-168; Christina Barr; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 101)
    - Quilter Janett Rice and her quilts at her home in Henderson, Nevada, October 17, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-169; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 102)
    - Quilts at the Desert Quilter's Annual Meeting held at the Henderson Convention Center, October 17, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-170 - S-2002-173; Christina Barr; 64 color slides (35mm) (Box 102)
    - Art Town Meeting hosted by the Nevada Arts Council at the Winchester Community Center in Las Vegas, November 1, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-174 - S-2002-175; Christina Barr; 32 color slides (35mm) (Box 102)
    - Art Town Meeting hosted by the Nevada Arts Council at the Winchester Community Center in Las Vegas; a couple of Mary Warner's paintings in the Las Vegas office OXS exhibit, November 2, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-176; Christina Barr; 13 color slides (35mm) (Box 102)
    - Setting up Day of the Dead altars for the altar contest at Prince of Peace Catholic Church in Las Vegas, November 2, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-177 - S-2002-178; Christina Barr; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 102)
    - Nevada Arts Council booth at the Vegas Valley Book Festival in Henderson, Nevada, November 2, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-179; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 102)
    - Day of the Dead altars for the altar contest at Prince of Peace Catholic Church in Las Vegas, November 2, 2002, AFC 2017/002: S-2002-180 - S-2002-185; Christina Barr; 106 color slides (35mm) (Box 103)
    - Shipibo artist Elena Nunta and her crafts at her home in Las Vegas, Nevada, February 4-6, 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-025 - S-2003-027; Christina Barr; 54 color slides (35mm) (Box 103)
    - Grant writing workshops held in the Las Vegas area, February 25, 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-028; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 103)
    - Costume maker Nancy Williams Baker at her costume supply and rental shop - Williams' Costume Supply Company - in Las Vegas, Nevada, February 25, 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-029; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 103)
    - Costume maker Nancy Williams Baker at her costume supply and rental shop - Williams' Costume Supply Company - in Las Vegas, Nevada, February 25, 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-030 - S-2003-034; Christina Barr; 71 color slides (35mm) (Box 104)
    - Zoria Zetaruk teaching a pysanky workshop at the East Las Vegas Community and Senior Center in Las Vegas, Nevada, June 11, 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-035; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 104)
    - Elena Nunta and her family at the Native American Festival at the Clark County Museum in Henderson, Nevada, June 11, 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-036; Christina Barr; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 104)
    - Quilter and cancer survivor Barb Johnston and her Quilts 4 Cancer project in Pahrump, June 11, 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-037 - S-2003-040; Christina Barr; 61 color slides (35mm) (Box 104)
    - Shadow Mountain Quilters' guild meeting in Pahrump, July 9, 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-041; S-2003-050; Christina Barr and Penny Rucks; 39 color slides (35mm) (Box 104)
    - Fabric art made by Ruth Ann Kirk in Pahrump, May 22, 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-051; Penny Rucks; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 105)
    - Nevada Arts Council sign and art in the OXS exhibit featuring Joanne Vuillemot in Las Vegas, May 27, 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-052; Penny Rucks; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 105)
    - [Unknown], June 2003 - October 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-053 - S-2003-059; Slide S-2003-058-024 is missing.; Penny Rucks and Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 153 color slides (35mm) (Box 105)
    - [Unknown], June 2003 - October 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-060 - S-2003-067; Slide S-2003-060-14 is missing.; Penny Rucks and Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 238 color slides (35mm) (Box 106)
    - [Unknown], June 2003 - October 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-068 - S-2003-071; S-2003-101 - S-2003-103; Slide S-2003-069-08 is missing.; Penny Rucks and Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 154 color slides (35mm) (Box 107)
    - Jeanne and Christina have dinner at the home of master artist Mohammad Darehbaghi and view traditional Persian paintings and drawings by Mohammad and apprentice Shahla. Also present are Mohammed's wife Azur and a cousin, and another folklife fieldworker, Irma Wynants, January 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-104; Andrea Graham; 3 color slides (35mm) (Box 107)
    - Visit to document Tai Chi apprenticeship project between master artist Andrew Lum and apprentice Billie Ann Sabala, June 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-105; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 38 color slides (35mm) (Box 107)
    - Site visit with master artist Sue Coleman and apprentice Cynthia Kannan (her daughter), pictured with Washoe willow baskets they have made, June 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-106; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 6 color slides (35mm) (Box 107)
    - Site visit with master artist Virgene Hardy at her home in Idaho, photos of the artist and baskets she has made, 2003, AFC 2017/002: S-2003-107; Jeanne Harrah Johnson; 30 color slides (35mm) (Box 107)
    - Site visit to master artist Ralph Charlie and apprentice Marlin Thompson at Ralph's home and workshop where they demonstrate how to made stone flints and arrows, March 25, 2004 - April 11, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-001; Anne F. Hatch; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 108)
    - Site visit to master artist Michelle Gibbons and her apprentice Evette Avilas, practicing Flamenco dance, April 11, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-002; Anne F. Hatch; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 108)
    - Site visit to Thunderbird Lodge (historical George Whittel estate), views of the lodge and its environs on the east (Nevada) shore of Lake Tahoe, April 11, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-003; Anne F. Hatch; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 108)
    - Student concert of Miguel Curiel, resident musician at the East Las Vegas Community Center; Clark County Fair at Logandale Fairgrounds, April 24, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-004; Anne F. Hatch; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 108)
    - Clark County Fair of items from the fine arts exhibit hall including quilts, weaving, tatting, crochet, and canning, at the Logandale Fairgrounds, April 24, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-005- S-2004-006; Anne F. Hatch; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 108)
    - Clark County International Food and Folklife Festival at the Clark County Government Building, this series include the Thai dancers and some crafts, May 18, 2004 - June 14, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-007- S-2004-009; Anne F. Hatch; 56 color slides (35mm) (Box 108)
    - Visit with Everett Pikyavitt at his home in Moapa, Nevada and three of the six Paiute baskets he made for Nevada Arts Council and the NTI exhibit "Texture and Weave." Apprenticeship final site visit with Elena Nunta (master of Peruvian Shipibo pottery, embroidery and beadwork), July 4, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-010; Anne F. Hatch; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 108)
    - Apprenticeship final site visit with Girtia Lukes (master African American quilter) and granddaughters, Reva and Reanna Lukes in Las Vegas; Las Vegas World Folk Fest First International Folk Festival of Las Vegas at Fremont Street Experience in downtown Las Vegas, July 4, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-011; Anne F. Hatch; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 108)
    - Las Vegas World Folk Fest First International Folk Festival of Las Vegas at Fremont Street Experience in downtown Las Vegas, July 4-21, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-012; Anne F. Hatch; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 108)
    - Elko Euzkaldunak Club, Annual National Basque Festival: Sunday Mass and Picnic in the Elko City Park, August 17, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-013- S-2004-014; Anne F. Hatch; 29 color slides (35mm) (Box 109)
    - Elko Euzkaldunak Club, Annual National Basque Festival: Sunday Mass and Picnic in the Elko City Park. Apprenticeship site visit with Edward McDade, Lee Reservation, Elko County. Moapa Reservation, Clark County, NTI purchase with Everette Pikyavitt, August 18, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-015; Anne F. Hatch; 18 color slides (35mm) (Box 109)
    - Tonopah Mining Museum, historic mining site in Tonopah, August 19, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-016; Anne F. Hatch; 19 color slides (35mm) (Box 109)
    - Armament yard displays, Fine Art project and Armament Museum, May 18, 2004 - June 14, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-017; Anne F. Hatch; 15 color slides (35mm) (Box 109)
    - Shoe tree north of Hawthorne on Highway 95; Virginia McCuin's ranch in Silver Springs; process of lost wax silver casting with Virginian McCuin, December 11, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-018; Anne F. Hatch; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 109)
    - Final apprenticeship site visit with Elaine Smokey (master), Rose Burns, and Carol Sanders making willow baby baskets, December 11, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-019; Anne F. Hatch; 16 color slides (35mm) (Box 109)
    - Annie receives an award from the Thai Performing Arts Association at Thai Cultural Dinner at Charleston Heights Arts Center; and OXS exhibit from Girtia Lukes, African American quilter at Nevada Arts Council Las Vegas offices, December 11, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-020; Anne F. Hatch; 9 color slides (35mm) (Box 109)
    - Procession for Our Lady of Guadalupe at Silver Dollar and Valley View, Las Vegas. Annie Hatch attended with Irma Wynants who documented with video, September 7, 2004, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-051- S-2004-053; Penny Rucks; 92 color slides (35mm) (Box 109)
    - [Unknown], April 2004 - February 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-054; Penny Rucks; 12 color slides (35mm) (Box 109)
    - [Unknown], April 2004 - February 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-055 - S-2004-080; Slides S-2004-059-013, S-2004-059-022, S-2004-060-014, S-2004-061-001, S-2004-067-001, and S-2004-078-022 are missing.; Penny Rucks; 667 color slides (35mm) (Box 110-112)
    - [Unknown], April 2004 - February 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-081 - S-2004-085; Slides S-2004-081-023, S-2004-082-017, and S-2004-085-033 are missing.; Penny Rucks; 167 color slides (35mm) (Box 113)
    - Site visit to master artist Zeny Ocean and apprentice Judith Robey to document Russian Balalaika apprenticeship, includes performance at Walden's Coffee House in Reno, March 3, 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2004-101; Anne F. Hatch; 40 color slides (35mm) (Box 113)
    - Master Apprenticeship final site visit with Daniel Ramos (FY2003) - teaching cradleboard making, specifically the shades to daughter Claudette Ramos. Mr. Ramos did not want to record his interview, so Annie wrote notes for the final report, April 23, 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-001; Anne F. Hatch; 12 color slides (35mm) (Box 113)
    - Mark Dahl's bit and spurs silver inlay. Part of LXS exhibitions in Carson City Legislative Offices. Artist from Elko County, photos taken in Las Vegas Nevada Arts Council Offices, April 28, 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-002; Anne F. Hatch; 13 color slides (35mm) (Box 113)
    - Portraits and images of Rosa's Mexican paper flower arrangements for Folklife Education Programs in Clark County, April 28, 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-003; Anne F. Hatch; 13 color slides (35mm) (Box 114)
    - Master artist FY2005 Kulvadee Sompong and apprentices Supatra Chemprachum and son at the International Food and Las Vegas Folklife Festival held at Clark County Amphitheater and Government Center, Las Vegas. Thai foodways and fruit and vegetable carving, April 28, 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-004; Anne F. Hatch; 20 color slides (35mm) (Box 114)
    - Twenty-four hour show fieldwork with Chris Simon, audio recorder, interviewed various employees at YESCO about work in sign production, July 13, 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-005- S-2005-007; Anne F. Hatch; 47 color slides (35mm) (Box 114)
    - Master artist Linda Johnson-Comas and Lynnaya Comas FY2005 at parks Indian Colony, Reno. Paiute basket weaving from collection of willow, preparation of materials to weaving starts and round baskets with lids (miniature), July 16, 2005, AFC 2017/002: S-2005-008; Anne F. Hatch; 12 color slides (35mm) (Box 114)